Surrounded by sharp cliffs
on three sides,
Windknight's Lot is a former medieval
training ground for knights.
Today, the town is
dominated by a prison
where its inmates mine for coal.
Agriculture and fishing
is the town's main lifeblood
But its population of
517 citizens and prisoners
may soon disappear!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters
swirling light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man
who follows his ambition…
…a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
EPISODE 5:
"THE DARK KNIGHTS"
The townspeople are hard at work.
Everything appears calm.
But I know Dio is
lurking somewhere.
What happened?
Well, Speedwagon
implored me so earnestly…
So I thought I'd help him create
just a small amount of Hamon.
But my finger must have slipped.
I'm terribly sorry, Speedwagon.
W-Why…you…
Baron Zeppeli, he's just a lad.
Rather spry for
a young bag snatcher, eh?
Don't just stand there ogling!
All of our money is in that bag!
That little devil!
A grab and dash in a single move.
Let's see…
I think he can serve us as a guide.
H-He's not sinking!
JoJo, the water's up to your knees!
Your Hamon energy
isn't quite there!
What a fine reverberation, JoJo.
You transmitted
your Overdrive perfectly.
Do you think this is the spot?
No, a couple of steps to the left.
I'll bet two quid on it.
Ouch!
Nice catch!
H-Huh? What's going on?
Who are you?
Something's odd about the boy.
Perhaps too much Hamon?
He's not the only thing
peculiar here.
Look around.
This is…!
A graveyard!
It seems we're the ones who've
fallen right into the catcher's mitt.
The boy was under
some sort of hypnosis.
Mr. Joestar, above you!
The sun has set.
Time for your lives
to disappear with it!
Dio!
T-They're crawling out!
I-I've been preparing myself
for this moment.
But this feeling of dread…
I'm pouring sweat!
And that arrogant monster is
standing there in the flesh!
He repaid Lord Joestar's fatherly love
with bloodstained betrayal!
His deeds will not go unpunished!
So that is Dio.
I see. He and his zombies
can't function during daylight.
So he hypnotized the boy
and lured us
to a location where
he has the advantage.
A man of such guile must never
be in possession of the mask.
We must destroy him!
Zombie knights!
Tell me your name!
P-Poco!
All right, Poco.
Hang on tight!
Let's move, JoJo!
Yes, sir!
Zoom Punch!
Amazing!
Dio Brando…
We've never met.
But I say this to the mask
that has awakened you.
We meet at last!
Hey, baby!
Plan on fighting from
that precarious perch?
Come down to meet me!
Don't push your luck, insect.
I stand, at the summit
of the living world,
a new organism born
for a new future!
As if I could lower myself to
the level of some pathetic human!
He's overwhelmingly evil!
A pure tyrant!
Once this wound has healed,
I will be free from all remnants
of that battle with JoJo.
Come, conjurer!
Your blood shall salve this wound!
Bastard! How many lives
have you ended to mend those scars?
How many slices of bread
have you eaten in your lifetime?
Dio!
Baron Zeppeli!
I will handle this.
You will suffer!
Solar Hamon, shine on me!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
He did it!
The Hamon is rippling
through Dio's arm!
Weakling! Weakling!
I-It's freezing!
No!
Zeppeli was it?
I see your energy depends on
the flow of your blood.
If I freeze your veins,
you will be powerless.
Know this—I have complete control
over my body.
I vaporized the moisture
in my arm after you touched it.
When the water vaporized,
it absorbed heat,
instantly freezing your arm.
And now!
Fool!
I'll crush your skull like a vase!
Dio, I'm cutting short
your vile ambition!
Dio, I feel your wicked blood
coursing through your veins.
I'll take that as a compliment.
You've done well
to stop my fist.
You've certainly grown stronger.
JoJo!
JoJo, if I were you,
I'd keep my hands to myself.
Take this, Dio!
The evaporation has frozen your veins.
Blood is cut off to your arm!
Your Hamon energy is worthless!
H-He's too strong!
He's five times as strong
as both of us together!
No! He'll freeze JoJo's arm
just like mine!
I can't let him hurt JoJo!
Baron Zeppeli!
T-This can't be!
S-So cold!
It's so cold it burns!
My skin is peeling…
It's as if I touched freezing metal!
Baron Zeppeli's arm!
Without circulation, it will rot!
He's invincible!
We can't use the Hamon of the Sun
to defeat him!
Is there another way?!
Hamon?
Breathing techniques?
If you want to huff and puff…
T-The ground is shaking!
…a much more suitable tribute
would be fanfare!
Tarukus! Dark Knight Blueford!
This fight is beneath me. Arise!
May their screams be my fanfare!
These demons!
Poco, hide!
In the 16th century, an ill-fated queen
was slain by Elizabeth I.
You, fierce knights who served
Queen Mary Stuart!
Settle this!
Exterminate these pests!
Do with them as you wish.
He lifted and crushed that boulder
with one finger!
Those two zombies
are heading for JoJo!
T-There's no way
he can fight them both.
If only blood was flowing
through my arm…
And if it was?
I could use my breathing technique
to heal my arm.
I must thaw…
Baron Zeppeli, all you need
is heat, right?
Y-You have a plan?!
How about this?!
Speedwagon!
In the Arctic,
people treat frostbite
by warming the affected areas
inside the body of a seal!
Zoom Punch!
Your blood is mine!
H-He's draining my blood!
Speedwagon, I …
I didn't come here
to slow you and Mr. Joestar down!
If you want to drink my blood,
then you'll have to lap up
some Hamon too!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
It's not working!
Is this bloodsucker
weakening my Hamon?!
I was wrong about you.
I thought you'd turn tail and run
at the first sign of danger.
I apologize.
Thank me when this fighting's over
and we're still alive!
Quickly! I-I must heal these wounds
and return to fighting form!
This knight's more chilling than
that bloody frozen arm of yours!
That blade dwarfs
Jonathan's 195 cm frame!
And that strange hair!
Those faces!
They're hiding something!
I've known many a fellow in my day,
and there's something overwhelmingly
sinister about those two!
Every Englishman knows the legendary
knights Tarukus and Blueford.
Even history bows to my will!
Long ago, in around 1565,
two monarchs were
contesting the throne:
Queen Elizabeth I…
and the beautiful,
23-year-old Mary Stuart.
The great knights Tarukus and Blueford
were her loyal vassals.
After losing their families in the war,
the knights found refuge with Mary
Regardless of strength,
a man seeks respite.
Not in romance,
but in something greater.
Mary gave them hope.
To her they swore their loyalty
and their lives.
But tragedy struck when Mary lost
her husband, Lord Darnley, unexpectedly
For Elizabeth, luck had struck.
Elizabeth accused Mary of mariticide.
The country turned against her,
and Mary was finally imprisoned
Tarukus and Blueford
fought to free her.
So Elizabeth bargained
with the two thorns in her side.
Turn yourselves in.
Then, and only then,
I shall spare Mary's life.
We cannot refuse.
I have no regrets.
The two were arrested…
…and executed
Allow me to send you blokes to hell with
a few last words: Mary's already dead!
You's were tricked!
See that lying over there
like a pile of rubbish?
That's your Mary.
Damn you to hell, Elizabeth!
You betrayed us!
With my final breath I curse you
and all of your descendants!
I lay my curse upon you!
The knights were beheaded
It's said Tarukus's neck
was so stiff with fury,
that the executioner broke several axes.
As for Blueford, his hair supposedly
coiled around his executioner's leg…
digging into his killer's flesh.
Their betrayal gave me goose bumps.
These legendary heroes
cursed the world.
I dug them up and gave them life!
Life as revenants
the devil himself would fear!
We swear loyalty to Master Dio!
We have come to end the world!
Death to everyone!
S-Such hatred!
Their scorn is growing!
Dio's made heroes into monsters!
Can we overcome their betrayal?
This Hamon of the flame…
I feel it intensifying!
Scarlet Overdrive!
A-Astounding!
I-I had forgotten about
Mr. Joestar's burden!
His father's death
and his hope for the future!
Our hope!
The hooligan has skill.
He'll be the perfect warm up
after our 300-year nap.
This one's flesh belongs to me!
I love the way cartilage
bursts between my teeth!
Another zombie!
This is no place for pawns.
W-What speed!
Master Dio, the spirit of
this young man is admirable!
I ask for the privilege of
putting an end to his life!
As you will.
Tarukus, stand aside.
The Dark Knight Blueford!
What ferociousness! What savagery!
He radiates skill and pride!
This is uncanny.
I learned about him in school.
And now he's coming to kill me.
I must steady my breathing
and relax my muscles!
The bastard! He's hiding his arms
behind his back!
Which will he attack with?
Or will he kick?
Incredible! He wields the sword
with his hair!
N-No!
Perceptive fellow.
He was able to dodge
my Danse Macabre hair.
How intriguing!
Mr. Joestar!
This is bad!
He can't breathe down there!
He can't use the Hamon!
We have to do something!
T-Tarukus!
Blast it!
We can't help Mr. Joestar!
This fight is over.
Blueford is unstoppable underwater.
My supervision is
no longer needed here.
I'll turn Windknight's Lot
into a town of zombies!
In just one day and one night, they will
spread to the whole of England!
I-I need to breathe
to create Hamon!
Just one breath!
Go! Swim to the surface!
We are equally matched.
You can't breathe,
and my armor weighs me down.
I won't use my sword.
We shall duel as heroes!
Make your move
before you drown!
Can I make it to the surface
before he does?
What are my odds?
Then, in the throes of death,
from deep within his psyche,
an explosive power ventured!
Another man would have struggled
toward the surface in agony
But JoJo was different.
He swam deeper,
to the bottom of the lake bed!
W-What is he thinking?
Hmm? Danny won't
let go of your toy gun?
It's because you're trying
to take it away
Change your thinking.
Try giving it to Danny instead
Windknight's Lot is a coal town.
That means the ground
settled long ago.
There!
There must be a rock with air trapped
beneath it from when it was above water!
I found it!
With this one breath…
Cut finely, beat of my blood!
I-Impossible!
The tables have turned on you!
Hamon travels
easily through water!
Underwater…
Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
NEXT EPISODE
Blueford is a mess!
I'm a master of slaughter!
This pain is nothing.
You will be destined to die.
Life Magnetism Overdrive!
EPISODE 6:
"TOMORROW'S COURAGE"